A Guide to the Papers of Michael Ryan, 1957-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Topical & Miscellaneous
  - Reviews of Michael Ryan's Books 1974, 1981-1989 (Box 19)
  - Warren Wilson College Course Evaluations re Michael Ryan 1982-1983, 1990 (Box 19)
  - University of Notre Dame Class Papers 1965, n.d. (Box 20)
  - University of Notre Dame Class Papers - Notes 1968-1980, n.d. (Box 20)
  - University of Notre Dame Class Papers - Plays n.d. (Box 20)
  - University of Notre Dame Class Papers - Short Stories n.d. (Box 20)
  - University of Notre Dame Examinations 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - University of Notre Dame Notebooks (16 Notebooks) 1965-1967 (Box 21)
  - Printed Material, including poetry magazines and periodicals, usually containing printed versions of Michael Ryan's poetry and articles (these examples have been copied and placed in the appropriate series of this collection) ca. 1965-1990 (Box 21)
  - Cassette Tapes
    - Michael Ryan: "final reading" at Cincinnati, Ohio, on the Ohio Poetry Circuit (T-782) 1981 Apr (Box 21)
    - Michael Ryan: at Modern Language Association Meeting, University of Arizona (T-783) 1981 Sep (Box 21)
    - Michael Ryan: poetry reading (T-784) 1986 Feb 16 (Box 21)
    - Michael Ryan: poetry reading, Virginia Writers' program, aired on WRFK-FM, Richmond, sponsored by the Virginia Commission for the Arts (T-785) 1987 (Box 21)
    - Michael Ryan: reading from God Hunger on "Fresh Air" program, aired on National Public Radio, WVTF-FM, Roanoke (T-785) 1989 Dec 2 (Box 21)
    - "Writing to be Heard," the Poetry of Michael Ryan (pilot). Introduction and interview by Gail Mazur, with readings by Ryan. Ryan explains his use of various poetic forms and the settings of several of his poems (T-786) n.d. (Box 21)